export const questionsData = [
  {
    Question: "Where is Bharat",
    Options: ["Asia", "Africa", "Europe", "North-America"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    Question: "What is Nepal",
    Options: ["Country", "State", "Village", "Town"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    Question: "19/2*4/2",
    Options: [19,44,66,33],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    Question: "Who is Modi",
    Options: ["Prime Minister", "President", "Army Chief", "Rail Minister"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    Question: "Is Plasma State",
    Options: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Neither"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    Question: "What is 12*12",
    Options: ["2561", "5682", "335", "144"],
    correctAnswer: 4,
  },
  {
    Question: "What is 4/2",
    Options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    Question: "color of Sky",
    Options: ["Blue", "Red", "Green", "Orange"],
    correctAnswer: "1",
  },
  {
    Question: "Is Tiger a Animal",
    Options: ["No", "Yes", "Human", "Bird"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    Question: "What is 21+21",
    Options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    correctAnswer: 4,
  },
];
